Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/mianawais99 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

ASP.NET MVC

React.js

Flutter

Languages

Punjabi (Native or Bilingual)
English (Professional Working)
Urdu (Native or Bilingual)

Certifications

Google Ads Search Certification Google Ads Display Certification Shopping ads Certification

Mian Awais

Full Stack Web Developer | Cloud Computing | Mobile App Developer

Sialkot

Summary

I'm final year student at COMSATS University Islamabad Wah Campus, pursuing a Computer Science Degree focused in Software Development.

As a Software Developer, having experience in developing several interactive Mobile Applications, Web Applications, CRM/ERP, Web Portals. I love sharing what I learn. I have various certification including certifications from AWS, Microsoft Azure, Google Cloud, Cisco networking academy, such as get connected IOT and cyber security. After learning these sills and getting hands on experience now I'm ready to get exposure of an office environment and Ready to utilize my skills in improving the cost and quality of software products.

- Expertise:

Full Stack Web Development | Android App Development | Flutter App Development | Cloud Computing | CMS | REST API

- -Web Frameworks
- ASP.NET MVC & .NET Core | CodeIgniter | Laravel | Yii | CakePHP | Node JS
- Concept & MethodologiesOOP | MVC | WaterFall | Agile | Data Structures | Automata
- -CMS

WordPress | Magento | Shopify | OpenCart | Joomla

- Cloud & Hosting Services
 AWS | EC2 | RDS | Lambda | ELB | Microsoft Azure | GCP | CPanel |
 SSH | FTP
- Management & VCS Skills

JIRA | SCRUM | Agile Development | SDLC | GIT | GitHub

Databases

- Relational: MySQL | MSSQL | PostgreSQL

- NoSQL: MongoDB | MariaDB

- Database Caching: Redis | Memcached

Frontend skills

- Vue.Js | React.JS | Bootstrap, Tailwind CSS
- Javascript | TypeScript | Jquery | ajax
- HTML5 (audio, video, canvas, geolocation, localstorage) | css3
- Adaptive layouts/frameworks Bootstrap, skeleton, Material Design;

To serve the society with the passion of volunteerism my goal is to utilize my scientific, technological, and programming skills, experiences, and interests to provide the exact Tech solution required.

Experience

Upwork

1 year 7 months

Mobile Application Developer
January 2021 - Present (1 year 3 months)

Full Stack Web Developer September 2020 - Present (1 year 7 months)

Fiverr

Full Stack Web Developer July 2019 - Present (2 years 9 months)

Punjab, Pakistan

Interns Pakistan

Internee: Front-End Developer January 2021 - March 2021 (3 months)

DigiSkills.pk

Trainee

September 2018 - August 2020 (2 years)

Pakistan

Education

COMSATS University Islamabad

Bachelor of Science - BS, Computer Science · (2018 - 2022)

Army Public School - (APSACS)

Fsc, Pre-Engineering · (2015 - 2017)